<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>pipes on venu&#39;s blog</title>
    <link>https://vkumbha.github.io/tags/pipes/</link>
    <description>venu&#39;s blog (pipes)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 10:20:34 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://vkumbha.github.io/tags/pipes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Pipes</title>
      <link>https://vkumbha.github.io/posts/pipes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 10:20:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vkumbha.github.io/posts/pipes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes. This is the state for terraform pipes.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
